so how many how many of you have had to
所以你们有多少人必须
write JavaScript form validation code
编写JavaScript表单验证代码
right so one of the things I want to
对，所以我想做的一件事
challenge you to think about as I go
挑战你去想我
through this talk is how much could you
通过这次演讲你能赚多少钱
reuse that exact same validation logic
重用完全相同的验证逻辑
inside your java application there's so
在您的Java应用程序内部
there's more and more tools to do this
有越来越多的工具可以做到这一点
kind of thing one of the classics is
经典之一是
Rhino that's been around a long time but
犀牛已经存在了很长时间，但是
in Java and in the VM now standard in
Java和VM中现在的标准
the VM there's a tool called nashorn
虚拟机中有一个名为nashorn的工具
anybody use natural one so national arne
任何人都使用天然的，所以全国范围内
is a much more high-performance
性能更高
JavaScript environment that's built into
内置的JavaScript环境
your JVM all the time I'm not talking to
我一直不跟你聊天的时候
that but there's also things like
那也有类似的事情
closure script which if you're writing
关闭脚本，如果您正在编写
closure you can compile closure into
您可以将闭包编译为
JavaScript with closure script but
带有关闭脚本的JavaScript，但是
there's also J sweet which J sweet you
还有一个J甜蜜，哪个J甜蜜的你
can write standard Java and it will
可以编写标准的Java，它将
compile your java into JavaScript that
将Java编译为JavaScript
you can then put into your browser pages
然后可以放入浏览器页面
so what about national or national horn
那国家或国家号呢？
like I said it's the JD kaise JavaScript
就像我说的是JD kaise JavaScript
solution ship standard in in the JDK in
解决方案运送标准在JDK中
the Java VM so there all the time and
Java VM，所以一直都有
there Oracle is putting serious effort
甲骨文正在认真努力
into making it high-performance in you
使其成为高性能
know in Java 7 you had invokedynamic
知道在Java 7中您具有invokedynamic
there's there's improvements going in in
有改进的地方
every Java release to improve the
每个Java版本以改进
performance of Nashua I won't tell you
Nashua的表现我不会告诉你
that it's at parity with nodejs
它与nodejs平价
but the gap is closing in many
但差距在缩小
situations it's going to perform
它要执行的情况
he knows close to node J s but it you
他知道靠近节点J，但是你
know the big difference with it is
知道最大的不同是
you're in the Java VM so you have access
您在Java VM中，因此您可以访问
to facilities in the Java VM that just
到Java VM中的设施
don't exist in node.js root right no js'
不存在于node.js根权没有js'
doesn't have threads right there are no
没有线程，就没有
threads for for node.js so anything you
node.js的线程，所以您
do with a its you know sending data back
使用它，您知道将数据发送回
and forth between workers you have to
您必须在工人之间来回
send essentially message objects and
发送本质上的消息对象
pass data by value but you know let's
按值传递数据，但我们知道
say you have something like the the
说你有类似的东西
disrupter ring buffer right which is a
破坏者环形缓冲区的权利是
super high performance Java ring buffer
超高性能Java环形缓冲区
structure it's used a lot like some
结构，它就像一些
stock trading applications use it
股票交易应用程序使用它
if you've got an 8 gigabyte in-memory
如果您有8 GB的内存
data structure that you're sharing
您共享的数据结构
between a bunch of threads that the
一堆线程之间
threads are simultaneously manipulating
线程正在同时操作
that you can't go handing an 8 gig
你不能去交8场演出
object between workers right so you can
反对工人之间的权利，所以你可以
do things with JavaScript in the Java VM
在Java VM中使用JavaScript进行操作
that you just can't even do in node.js
甚至在node.js中都做不到的
right just not even possible so a apples
对，甚至不可能，所以一个苹果
to apples performance comparison is hard
与苹果的性能比较很难
to make because the facilities are
因为设施
simply not there and how easy is it to
根本不在那里，这有多容易
get going
出发
so these two lines kind of show you a
所以这两行告诉你
super simple example of doing a little
超级简单的例子
Java Script the you get asked for a new
Java脚本，要求您提供新的
script engine from the script engine
脚本引擎中的脚本引擎
manager you ask for it by name Nashorn
经理，您要求的名称是Nashorn
and then here you go engine eval and you
然后在这里您进行引擎评估，而您
can put any JavaScript you want in there
可以在其中放置任何想要的JavaScript
and it'll run it it will convert it to
它将运行它将转换为
Java bytecode and execute it but you can
Java字节码并执行它，但是您可以
not only you know spit something to
不仅你知道吐东西
standard out if you instantiate an
如果实例化一个
object in JavaScript here and return
JavaScript中的对象然后返回
that you're going to get back an object
你将要取回一个物体
handle in Java that you can call methods
Java中可以调用方法的句柄
on and you can even pass Java objects
甚至可以传递Java对象
into and have that JavaScript object
进入并拥有该JavaScript对象
call methods on your Java object and it
Java对象及其上的调用方法
all works seamlessly right it's all just
所有功能都可以无缝进行，仅此而已
more objects in the Java VM so that's
Java VM中有更多对象，因此
one of the things I want you guys to
我希望你们能做的一件事
think about is don't think about it as
考虑是不要考虑
like there's JavaScript world in Java
就像Java中的JavaScript世界一样
world Java is a human language the Java
世界Java是人类语言Java
VM does not run Java source code right
VM无法正确运行Java源代码
it runs Java bytecode
它运行Java字节码
well Nashorn compiles JavaScript into
Nashorn将JavaScript编译成
Java bytecode so javascript with Nashorn
Java字节码所以Nashorn的JavaScript
is just another way to produce Java
只是产生Java的另一种方式
bytecode so if you have already have
字节码，所以如果您已经有
validation logic if you already have
验证逻辑（如果您已经拥有）
value in your existing JavaScript that
现有JavaScript中的价值
you've had to write for web applications
您必须为Web应用程序编写
before you rewrite it in Java take a
在用Java重写之前，请先
step back and go like can we just use
退后一步，就像我们可以使用
that do we have to rewrite that and
那我们必须重写它，并且
really think about that right because if
真的考虑那个权利，因为如果
you get in the position of that you're
你的位置是
not only doing your validation logic
不仅要执行验证逻辑
let's say in in your web application but
假设在您的Web应用程序中
now you're talking about doing an iOS
现在您正在谈论做一个iOS
native app and you're talking about
本机应用程序，您正在谈论
doing an Android native app you know
做一个您知道的Android本机应用程序
that you're going to have to keep your
你将不得不保持你的
objective-c version of that validation
该验证的Objective-C版本
like logic your java version of that
就像逻辑上那样
validation logic your java script
验证逻辑您的Java脚本
that validation logic that's all
验证逻辑就是全部
engineering hours and those are all
工程时间，这些都是
opportunities for failure right you can
失败的机会就可以
have drift between your versions and
在您的版本和
that's how you get serious bugs in your
这就是您遇到严重错误的方式
platform so you want to you know don't
平台，所以您想知道不
repeat yourself single source of truth
重复自己的真相
can you reuse that code and that's what
您可以重用该代码吗？
that's what isomorphic applications are
这就是同构应用
about it's Ekman script five I think
关于这是埃克曼剧本，我认为是五个
there's some Xmas scripts six coming but
有一些Xmas脚本六个，但是
you can you know like you can run
你可以知道你可以跑步
Express with Babel like you can use
可以使用Babel进行表达
webpack and Babel and produce with the
webpack和Babel，并与
transpiler that will work on nashua so
可以在nashua上运行的转译器
you can use Eknath script six constructs
您可以使用Eknath脚本的六个构造
they're just transpiled so there's some
他们只是被转译，所以有一些
performance considerations but like I
性能方面的考虑，但和我一样
said natural one is definitely under
说自然的肯定在
active development Oracle is definitely
积极发展Oracle绝对是
gets it the JavaScript in Java is a big
得到它Java中的JavaScript很大
deal and then they are pursuing that
交易，然后他们追求
because you know the reality is for Java
因为您知道现实是针对Java的
and the browser applets are gone right
浏览器小程序正确
nobody's even thinking about I mean
没人在想我
before there and now that even that
在那之前，现在，即使那样
they're officially gone nobody was
他们正式走了，没人
really that happy about using applets
使用小程序真的很高兴
for a while now so the web is just
现在有一段时间了，所以网络只是
getting to be a bigger and bigger deal
变得越来越大
and javascript is everywhere you know
Javascript无处不在
with and with tools like PhoneGap Apache
与诸如PhoneGap Apache之类的工具一起使用
Cordova anybody ever play with that you
科尔多瓦有人玩过你吗
can you can build a simple web
你可以建立一个简单的网站吗
application and package it for the web
应用程序并将其打包为网络
store you can put it into the Apple
商店，您可以将其放入Apple
Store put it in the Android store so
商店把它放在Android商店中
there's these powerful platforms that
这些强大的平台
are emerging to let you move your code
正在出现让您移动代码
between all kinds of different
各种不同之间
environments you can get nodejs kind of
你可以得到nodejs的环境
style work with yeah
是的
yes yes so you can you should be able to
是的，所以你应该可以
call any method on any java object from
从中调用任何Java对象上的任何方法
javascript using Nashorn so anything you
使用Nashorn的javascript
could write in Java I believe and I
我相信我可以用Java编写
believe you should be able to MIT you
相信你应该能够MIT
can do things like manipulate threads
可以做诸如操纵线程之类的事情
from JavaScript in using Nashorn like
从JavaScript中使用Nashorn
you know if you have a handle to those
你知道你是否有能力
objects you can call you just you can
你可以打电话给你的东西
call methods on Java objects so anything
Java对象上的调用方法
you can do via calling methods on Java
您可以通过在Java上调用方法来完成
objects you may you may have to do some
您可能需要做的事情
casting you may have to go depending out
铸造你可能必须去取决于
like if you try to do something really
例如，如果您尝试真正做某事
low-level I don't have a Pat answer in
低级别的我没有Pat的答案
terms of you know will it be easy but
你知道的话会很容易，但是
you should be anything you can do in
你应该做任何你能做的
Java you should be able to do in
您应该能够使用的Java
JavaScript there may be some like there
JavaScript可能有一些类似的东西
may be some interesting things when it
可能是一些有趣的事情
comes to getting if you have like you
如果你喜欢你就会得到
know a method that you're using casting
知道您正在使用转换的方法
you know to that the type detection
你知道类型检测
plays a big role in it it may get a
在其中扮演重要角色，可能会
little complicated but so you may have
有点复杂，但您可能会有
to do something like write an adapter
做类似写适配器的事情
class in Java that like gives JavaScript
Java中的类，它提供了JavaScript
little help in hand just to understand
几乎没有什么帮助，只是为了了解
the typing system
打字系统